Satyam Rawat

Experience/Visual Designer

I'm focused on creating meaningful experiences through design.

I am a passionate UI/UX designer, backed up knowledge in front end Development.

While design comes easy to me, I work hard to convert the ideas into reality by designing websites, web apps and mobile apps myself.

Work Experience

April 2017 - Oct 2019

Sr. UI/UX Designer - eConz IT Services

Led the design team. Worked closely with *Caterpillar*, *FG Wilson & Toyota India*.

Caterpillar India (https://catmachine.co.in/):

Recreated the UI and optimised the UX to explore the products & services in minimum steps. Which caused to *increse the site traffic* and quality leads by +48%

FG Wilson Asia Pacific (https://www.fgwilson.com.sg/):
Designed & developed websites and Dealer locator system for FG
Wilson Asia Pacific. *Enhanced the UX* to ease the product portfolio explore journey.

Toyota India:

Developed landing pages for Toyota India. Also helped the development team to create the lead capturing system.

Sept 2015 - Feb 2017

UI Designer - Easeit Technologies

Worked here as a UI designer & Front-end developer. Learnt about user experience and its impacts, various design systems & best practices and their implementation.

Aug 2014 - Jul 2015

Web/Content Designer - ZOC Technologies

As an intern I started up my career from here.

Contact

satyamrawat03@gmail.com +91 9983 177 466

Linkedin:

/satyam-rawat-a5385283

Portfolio:

www.satyamrawat.com

Education

Bachelor of Technology (Computer Science)

Mewar University, Chittorgarh(Rajasthan)

2010-2014

Skills

Design

User Research
Wireframing & Prototyping
Visual Design
Interaction Design
Usability Testing

Tools

Pen & Paper, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Sketch, Adobe XD, Figma, InVision, Justinmind, Office, Keynote

Programming

HTML & CSS JavaScript Bootstrap 4, jQuery JSON & Git

Deployment

Google Cloud Platform(GCP)

AWS

cPanel & Linux OS(CLI)